{
    "subject": "resource/Dell",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsidiary",
    "object": "resource/Alienware",
    "human_readable": "Dell has a subsidiary called Alienware.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.936259925365448,
            "question": "Is Alienware a part of Dell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8840237855911255,
            "question": "Does Dell have any other subsidiaries besides Alienware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883821427822113,
            "question": "How does Alienware benefit from being a subsidiary of Dell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8366917371749878,
            "question": "What is the name of Dell's subsidiary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8038162589073181,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Dell and Alienware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7371364831924438,
            "question": "Which company owns Alienware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5364387631416321,
            "question": "Is Alienware known for gaming computers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5292103290557861,
            "question": "Name a technology company that has a subsidiary."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42081648111343384,
            "question": "Who is the parent company of Alienware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34972432255744934,
            "question": "What type of products does Alienware primarily sell?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dell has a subsidiary called Alienware.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8588_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the parent company of Alienware?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8588_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a technology company that has a subsidiary.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8588_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alienware known for gaming computers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8588_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8588_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Alienware is indeed a subsidiary of Dell, such as stating \"Alienware is a leading producer of high-performance gaming laptops and desktops based in Miami, Florida. The company was founded in 1996 and was acquired by Dell in 2006. Since then, Alienware has operated as a subsidiary of Dell\" and \"Dell holds ownership of Alienware as a parent company\". Therefore, the statement that Dell has a subsidiary called Alienware is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}